PERSONAL PROFILE

I am an undergraduate at DigiPen Institute of Technology pursuing a Bachelors of Science in Computer Science in Real-Time Interactive Simulation. I have multiple relevant experience in gameplay programming / game engine architecture and harbor a deep passion for developing games and applications!

SKILLS

- C++
- C
- C#
- Machine Learning
- Python
- Unity
- ReactJS
- CSS
- JavaScript
- HTML
- OpenGL

AWARDS

Mind Over Matter - Winner for Best 2D Visual Design (DigiPen)

Mind Over Matter - Finalist for Best Sophomore Game (DigiPen)

Mind Over Matter - Finalist for Best 2D Graphics Technology (DigiPen)

Mind Over Matter - Finalist for Best User Interface (DigiPen)

FishieProtecc - Finalist for Gumi Asia's Best Freshman Game (DigiPen)

Dean's Honor List throughout 2018 - 2021 (DigiPen)

YOU CAN FIND ME AT



https://weixianglim.github.io/

in linkedin.com/in/weixiang-lim

WEI XIANG LIM

ASPIRING GAMES PROGRAMMER AND DEVELOPER

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

TEACHING ASSISTANT

DigiPen Institute of Technology | Feb 2018 - Mar 2021

- Assist professors in guiding and teaching students (Math, CS)
- · Grading and providing feedback to student assignments
- Hold TA sessions to guide students after school
- Hold private consultations with students

PROGRAMMING INTERN

Neeuro | Sep 2015 - Nov 2015

- Worked with the existing Neeuro team on the Memorie app
- · Worked in Unity Engine to develop minigames for the app
- Fully developed a sister prototype application with Unity
- Worked with and tested Neeuro's SenzeBand technology

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

DIGIPEN INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY

BS in Computer Science Real-Time Interactive Simulation

- Studied advanced C++ and various programming techniques
- Technical Lead for 4 game projects
- Built 2D & 3D game engines from the ground up for the game projects
- Received multiple awards and nominations for the 2D puzzle platformer - Mind Over Matter

NANYANG POLYTECHNIC

Diploma in Digital Entertainment Technology | 2014 - 2016

- NYP Scholarship holder
- Studied extensive C++
- · Worked with popular industry game engines
- Studied various games development techniques
- Introduced to PlayStation 4 development